哈囉?
我父親...
又死了.
- 大使館你好.
- 存取密碼 2-2...
密碼是 2-2-4-5-4.
還有效嗎?
有.
我需要追蹤一通電話
一分鐘前打給我的.
好.
哈囉?
她剛打電話給你.
我不知道發生了什麼事.
我們需要你現在來特拉維夫一趟.
你他媽的開什麼玩笑?
到底發生了什麼事.
不要透過電話.
你得搭飛機過來.
不, 不, 那...
那是不可能的.
我在這裡跟你見面.
湯瑪士, it's 喬.
Jesus!
They brought you in?
They did.
How are you, 喬? How's Netta?
She's fine.
Still in remission.
Listen, 湯瑪士,
the situation is getting...
I'm not flying anywhere, 喬.
You don't have to fly anywhere.
There's a safe house in 科隆.
They'll give you the details.
I'm heading there now.
Thanks for coming
on such a short notice.
- I'm Daniel.
- 湯瑪士.
- Hi.
I remember.
Why did she call you?
I don't know.
- She knows you're out?
- I don't know.
Are you gonna tell me
what's going on?
She said, "My father died.
Again." And hung up.
What does it mean?
"Her father dying"
was her pullout code from Iran.
Did her father really die?
Her father died four days ago,
near 倫敦.
She slipped out of 以色列,
attended his funeral,
and disappeared
right after that.
Disappeared?
She could be anywhere now.
I'm only talking to 喬.
- He's on his way.
- He's retired.
Yeah, so am I. For fuck's sake,
you had him call me,
I'm only talking to him.
Whatever, 湯瑪士.
Are you pulling me out?
No.
You always wanted
to get your hands on him.
But you got your hands on him.
- See how that worked out.
- Fuck you.
Isn't it nice to be needed?
I've been waiting for this call
ever since you graduated.
- Hey, watch out.
- You can have this room.
Anything you need,
we will be right here.
Mm-hm.
Listen, until the call
this morning,
I hadn't heard from her
in over a year.
湯瑪士, nobody is blaming you
for anything.
This is about assessing
her motives.
You were the person
closest to her.
You're crucial.
Look, let's just go over this,
step by step.
Let them do the grunt work.
We need to get into her head.
We have an advantage over them.
You know her and I know you.
Do you consider yourself Jewish?
My father was half Jewish.
I read in your file
that you were adopted.
Is that relevant?
Do you know who
your biological parents were?
Mm-mm.
Were you brought up Christian
by your mother?
To some extent.
We should develop that.
When they assigned her to me,
she was working out of 萊比錫, doing basic stuff.
It was my idea
to send her to 德黑蘭,
get her into
the nuclear division.
It wasn't easy
to convince HQ.
She did have
a very unusual biography
for a Mossad operative.
Born in 倫敦.
Her father, a British citizen.
Her mother, German,
基督徒浸信會,
who died when 瑞秋 was 12.
I don't remember much
of 倫敦.
What I think I remember
is probably
from pictures I saw later.
We moved to Boston
when I was six,
加拿大 when I was twelve.
That's when my mom
started chemo.
So where are you from?
Only place
I've ever felt at home,
at least for a moment,
is 以色列.
Why?
I don't know.
You know, my mom
always used to talk about it.
She volunteered
in a kibbutz there in the '70s.
It was a big thing for Germans
to do at that time.
Have you ever lived there?
She was in a relationship
with an 以色列i medical student she'd met in 倫敦.
That was her first time
in the country.
When they split up, she stayed.
She had no real plans. She was kind of a drifter.
When she extended her work visa,
someone
in the organization noticed.
I mean, she immediately
attracted attention,
passports,
language skills.
A lack of any center
or real roots anywhere.
The recruiter got a sense
that she was eager to belong.
Eager to do
something significant.
We gave her
a fully authenticated
Australian passport.
Built her a whole new identity
around that.
Early years near 雪梨,
growing up in 加拿大.
She spent a year in 萊比錫
establishing that identity.
Her cover,
an English and French teacher.
哈囉.
Her first assignment
was to get a work permit
in 德黑蘭,
sponsored by
a local language school there.
For a Mossad operative
to enter Iran so early
in their career is unusual,
but I had confidence in her.
This making you uncomfortable?
Mm-mm.
Primary screening
is about 30 seconds.
If you got a secondary,
that's hours.
A secondary can be triggered
by nervousness
or any kind of inconsistency.
So luggage, length of stay,
profession, ticket class,
they all have to match.
You shouldn't look like
you've just stepped out
of a mall.
How close are you
to your father?
Why? What do you mean?
You should always
establish cover
with close family members
before unusual absences.
Oh, we're not close.
Still.
What?
All right.
I'll do it, fine.
You live alone, don't you?
Do I?
Hmm, I don't know.
You always schedule meetings
on weekends.
Your predecessor never did.
Well, I think
if it is 24-7 for you,
then it should be for me, too.
So even if you were married,
you'd see me on a weekend?
I'm probably
not gonna sleep tonight.
You're gonna do great.
You're the best person
for this assignment.
Thank you for saying that.
- 哈囉.
Know anybody in 德黑蘭?
No, uh...
I e-mailed with the person
who hired me.
You are staying where?
Hotel Esteghlal.
Hey!
I'm sorry?
New?
Oh, some. I lost my luggage
on my flight to Berlin.
Taxi!
哈囉?
哈囉, Miss Currin.
Our spa is open
and at your disposal.
We also want to let you know
that we have
all kinds of drinks.
Not just what's in the menu,
I couldn't sleep that night.
I imagined them entering,
dragging me out.
I imagined being hanged.
I remember thinking,
I'm all alone.
You know, it's just me
and the rest of the world.
Everybody must know who I am.
How could they not?
And then I realized,
as I was standing there,
peeping, that...
I had nothing to hide.
You know I was just that person
who came here to teach.
That's it.
Nothing else.
I just decided
I wasn't gonna be afraid.
That's a temporary work permit.
Okay, file all your receipts,
I'll handle the reports.
Take a couple of days off.
You did good.
Okay.
What's that perfume?
What do you mean?
It's not the one you left with.
Was it clear at this point
that she was going to go
long-term to Iran?
No.
She made some contacts there
and was liked
at the language school.
But I needed her to be part of
one of the big operations first.
I needed the higher-ups to pay attention to her.
安潔拉, this is 史蒂芬.
史蒂芬, 安潔拉.
Staying one night
in uusseldorf,
for shopping
and waiting for a flight.
Your room number is 507.
Already checked in.
You really don't speak
any Hebrew?
What's it to you?
史蒂芬 is really lousy
at cover work.
So don't let him open his mouth.
Security cameras
and the layout
is here, here, here, and there.
This is a time table
when we can access them.
- And the lobby,
- Here?
if you sit here,
you have the best view.
How long are we supposed to stay at the bar?
That's your call.
Just long enough
for people there
to get a sense of your presence.
Aren't we supposed to talk?
Even a little?
This is Anton ooska.
He's been helping Iran
since the '90s.
Uranium enrichment program.
That's the only photo
we have of him.
It was probably taken
15 years ago.
Positive ID is crucial.
If he's in the bar tonight,
you will be closest to him.
There'll be another team
cross-validating
with telephoto lenses.
How was your practice?
It was good.
Uh, when I went to this corner,
people usually stood here.
I could easily squeeze
in between them
to get to the panel.
And I wasn't even pregnant then.
So elevators A, B, C, D.
Text 史蒂芬
before you get in
to let him know
which elevator you're in.
What if you need
to let 史蒂芬 know
for any reason to abort?
If I have to abort I say,
"Here you are."
I exit to the right
in front of him.
I take him away.
He's my husband,
he was waiting for me.
All goes well,
I exit to the left,
get out of his shot.
Now, we don't execute
at any cost.
Something
is not according to plan,
you have the right
to call it off.
Exit?
Emergency stairs.
We wait here and pickup is here.
Right.
Miss, we're going up.
- We're going up.
- Oh. Oh, up.
Uh, no matter,
I take a tour with you.
Uh, sorry.
Um, can you press L, please?
Thank you.
There you are.
No, please!
哈囉.
I'm 瑞秋.
Rosita.
Hi.
Hey!
- Hi.
- Pleasure.
I wanted to meet you
for a while.
- I'm Ronnie.
- Pleasure.
We actually met before,
once in training.
This is Dan.
- Nice to meet you.
- Hi.
No chance you met him before.
Beautiful day.
I missed the 以色列i weather.
It's really nice to meet you.
You haven't been to 以色列
since you worked with him.
Oh, I work out of Germany.
You didn't even visit.
You should visit more
to connect to the place,
to the people.
You're one of us now.
There aren't that
many foreigners there,
so everybody's constantly trying
to help you.
Prove that Iranians
are not like what
Westerners imagine them to be.
They can be nice
to the point
of driving you crazy.
Did it make it more difficult
for you to live your cover?
Not really.
Um, just have to learn
how to handle it.
Focus on the job,
the students.
Be who you are.
Hmm.
You're very talented.
It's not easy to stand out
in our organization.
How do you feel about
a long-term assignment
in 德黑蘭?
Yeah, he just wanted
to look you in eye
when he asked you.
Danke.
Didn't even know your name
till recently.
Would you stay on as my handler?
Of course.
So did you give them
an answer yet?
I was so excited
I couldn't speak.
I can't believe I'm here.
"Here"?
Doing this, you know.
It does feel different
knowing that you're there
for a long time.
Now, I walk around a lot.
I feel like that's important,
you know,
to get a sense of the city.
Where things are.
How to interact with people.
How not to attract attention.
Keep to myself.
I'm consciously making an effort
to learn everyday habits here.
It's getting easier.
The apartment
I rented in Pasdaran
is, is perfect.
It's practical. I like it.
It's comfortable.
Makes perfect sense for a single Western woman to live there.
There's lots of cafes
I like to sit in.
Shops I like to shop in.
You know, the more
I have people around me,
I feel like I belong.
瑞秋.
Mahshid wanted
to ask you something.
She wanted to know
if you'd have come
dinner with us.
I'd love to. Thank you.
I do like it there.
I like 德黑蘭.
I'm alone
most of the time, but...
You know I don't feel lonely.
I can't explain it.
Every time I come back to Germany to see you,
I feel more
and more out of place.
And I can't wait
to get back to Iran.
Pants.
- "Pants."
- Mm-hmm.
It did feel very boring at first
after all the work
we've done here.
But, um...
You know, my work is so detailed
and fragmented.
After a while,
I really realized
that it helps me focus
and occupies my mind.
Thank you.
I'm an English teacher.
Is it okay if I work here?
I like to get out of the house.
Sure, no problem.
Look at this.
It's weeks
of tracking the coming and going
of Reza Vahidi.
- The Minister of Defense.
- Yeah.
Did she know that? Did...
Did she know
who she was tracking?
She had no idea.
After six months carrying out
small, disconnected missions
like this,
I felt that her routines
were set.
That her cover was stable.
That she was stable.
She was ready
for the next thing.
That's when we decided to approach Razavi Electronics.
Farhad Razavi.
"The wallet...
- is gone."
- Is.
"Three coins...
- Are.
- ...are missing."
"Everyone...
- Are...
- Is.
- ...is here."
- But "everyone" are many people.
Hey, hey, hey.
It's actually
a really good question, Shirin.
Does anybody know
why it's "is" and not "are"?
- Ali?
- Mm?
You know?
Come with me.
My Uncle Farhad, he has a BMW.
- Wow, really?
- Mm-hm.
All right, well.
Let's see who gets
to spot him first.
Okay.
瑞秋?
There he is.
Well.
- Goodbye!
- Bye, Ali!
I am sorry I am late.
My sister,
she called me just now.
No problem.
You've worked with Ali
after school?
Yeah, twice a week.
You give
the one-to-one lesson, too?
One-on-one lessons, yeah.
Wait, wait.
My name is Farhad.
I'm 瑞秋. Nice to meet you.
I need your help.
I think your English
is pretty good.
No, I, uh...
I've worked in Europe a lot.
I want to...
I want to be loose.
You know, free.
You want to be "loose"?
Uh...
You see?
I'm going to drop Ali
to my sister's now.
Uh, maybe
you can give me lesson later?
Oh, I'm sorry.
I'm really busy here today.
Ah.
Tomorrow?
Shall we begin?
Tell me about yourself.
No, no, no, uh...
I pay, I decide what we talk.
"I'm paying, I should decide
what we talk about."
Uh...
If you're going to be impolite,
at least express
yourself correctly.
Okay.
I'm paying, so I should decide
what we talk about.
Very good.
- Oh, yes, please. Thank you.
- Yes.
What do you do?
It'll help me to find out
what your needs are.
You are in Iran, how long?
A while.
You did not learn not to ask
questions like that?
"Haven't you learned
not to ask questions like that?"
What do you wanna talk about?
Tell me about yourself.
That's okay?
- Mm-hm.
- Really?
You just make up the rules
that suit you?
I'm so sorry.
The rules here are invented
to suit me.
So...
Tell me something.
Something personal.
Personal, um...
I was adopted.
My parents
are not my biological parents.
You're born where?
I was born in Australia.
But we left
when I was young.
Six.
I grew up in Vancouver.
You are lucky.
You lived in different places.
Yeah, well, you know...
I'm jealous of people
that have a home.
Place.
Friends they know
since childhood.
So why are you here?
I was teaching in 萊比錫.
But honestly, it was really,
really boring and...
I don't know.
You know?
德黑蘭, there's something
I really like here.
Hmm.
You know what it is?
The people here
all have many secrets.
Do they?
There's too many rules in Iran.
So...
If, uh... If you want to drink,
you keep it secret.
You marry a woman who is a...
You understand.
She, she had sex.
You keep it secret.
If you go to a party
or a cultural thing
too controversial,
keep it secret.
You don't want to fast
during Ramadan?
Eat in secret.
It's the way of life here.
Like a second nature.
瑞秋?
Hi.
I wanted to see if, um...
Do you wanna have tea?
Are you okay?
Oh, yes. I'm sorry.
I'm just a bit dizzy.
It's the weather.
Always happens to me.
It's the man from the upstairs.
His son is a criminal.
He often comes here to hide.
哈囉?
There's a party tonight.
Like the one I told you of.
Will you come?
Just like that, huh?
I will pick you up.
My friends want to meet you.
I didn't know
I could dress like that.
Hey!
This is my friend 瑞秋.
瑞秋, this is Aarmeen.
Nice to meet you.
- This is Bita.
- Nice to meet you.
Yeah.
What?
These are my childhood friends,
- Nawser and Zoya.
- Nice to meet you.
This is 瑞秋? Salaam.
- Welcome.
- Nice to meet you.
Oh, I don't want that.
- It's okay.
- It's no help, really.
瑞秋.
Everyone does.
- No, I'm, I'm good.
- Just one.
If you insist, I'm leaving.
Okay.
Wow!
Another one?
It's my first time
having alcohol in Iran.
Drinking is illegal here, right?
Your ecstasy dealer
is also your alcohol dealer.
Like this guy with the hat,
they dance.
I'll go.
Hey.
Good morning.
Is this your brother?
Mm-hm.
What do you care?
Your father called the embassy.
Started asking questions.
So I had to talk to him.
Explain everything.
You did what?
That's private, 湯瑪士,
all right?
And that's none
of your goddamn business.
He told me
you're not adopted.
That was just a game, 湯瑪士.
A stupid game
I used to play as a teenager.
It's nothing.
You said in your file
that you're adopted.
I didn't mean to lie.
It's just something my friend
and I used to say in school.
And I'm sure
it was written somewhere.
So I just automatically...
So from a teenager till now,
a grown woman,
you are still saying
you are adopted?
- So what?
You told me you're adopted.
You basically
told this organization
that you are adopted.
When I started working
for the Mossad,
all I did was...
They just used my name
to rent apartments in Berlin.
All right? I never imagined
it would go this far.
It was just a stupid lie.
That you're still telling now.
- Yes.
- Why?
I don't have anything else
to say to that.
God, and you don't
even seem bothered
that, one, you didn't inform
family member
of your association with us,
which you said you would do.
And, two, you've lied about
something pretty major
to do with your background.
Now, this job is all about
being able
to be completely honest
with the people
you're supposed to trust.
You can lie to the world,
but in here, you tell the truth.
To this organization,
you tell the truth.
And to me, you tell the truth.
'Cause even shitty,
little details like this,
it all matters,
because I have to trust you.
I have to completely trust you.
You're right.
I'm sleeping with Farhad.
You're what?
I slept with him.
I mean I'm still sleeping
with him, but...
You were just supposed
to tutor him!
You didn't report this.
I'm reporting it now.
That was a key moment.
We suddenly realized
we couldn't control her fully.
And she wanted
to make that point.
She was like,
"If I wanna sleep with the guy,
I'll sleep with the guy."
She had a life there.
So what do you do?
You let her dictate like that?
You tolerate a relationship
you have absolutely
no handle on?
Or you pull her out?
Lose everything?
What do you do?
Especially not with her.
What do you mean "not with her"?
She was just supposed to give
the guy private lessons.
We all know
what she was supposed to do.
The question is what...
I'll handle it.
Are they gonna start
doubting me?
Of course not.
They just don't like surprises.
You're so good
at giving away nothing.
Did you bring him
to your apartment?
No, we went to a party
and back to his place.
So tell me something about him.
He wears more cosmetics
than I do.
Razavi Electronics
was a legit company
when we started.
Farhad Razavi,
we took him for a lightweight,
a rich playboy.
But we discovered
that when the Iranians
try to buy
a restricted technology,
they like doing it
through legit companies.
So we started steering a lot of offers towards Razavi.
This was all part
of operation
"Business as Usual."
We were grooming
Razavi Electronics
to become
an unwitting middleman
between us and the Iranian Secret Service.
For that,
we needed to infiltrate
their internal network.
It's a pretty simple task given they were a civilian company.
Oh, I'm sorry,
I got lost.
Do you know where the exit is?
- It's there.
- Oh.
Thank you.
So?
Can you do this work?
Is that you?
How old?
How much do you want per hour?
Call me a cab?
I will drive you.
Can you wait five minutes?
I'll wait for you outside.
I need some air.
Hey, uh...
Are people looking at me?
Is it okay for an unmarried man
and an unmarried woman
to be seen together?
Please,
stop worrying about this.
Nobody cares.
Okay.
That flag in your booth,
is it Azerbaijan?
You know the flag?
Yeah.
Never been there.
Once, I lived there,
for many years.
Can I try your brand?
It's strong.
Thank you.
Shit.
If he didn't give me so much...
...I would have finished
my day 30 minutes before.
I'm sorry.
What's...
It's too much politeness,
too much flattery.
"How can I ever thank you?
I would never dream
to trouble you."
Yeah, I've wasted
half my day on this.
"How can I ever thank you?
I would never dream
to trouble you."
Are you here by yourself
all night?
That is what I'm good for.
Smoking and...
letting the time pass.
My mom always used to say...
She died of cancer.
She always used to say
that we let time slip.
You know, let it pass us by.
My brother, same thing.
He is younger,
he is going to die soon.
And all he wants
is more time.
And I have all the time.
Too much.
I don't need it.
Yeah, well...
A person who knows
they're about to die,
that's the worst.
Best to die like that.
Yes.
Why only have two guards?
You know, switch,
play backgammon...
Money.
Just me.
Yes. Got it!
Yes!
Shit.
Oh, Nima.
You scared me.
I got locked in the bathroom
after work today.
Just got out.
I'm gonna tell Farhad
about it tomorrow.
Have a good night.
Shit!
Asleep already?
Almost.
Everything okay?
Maybe you want
to come over?
Um...
I'm tired, you know.
I have that early
makeup class tomorrow.
That fucking class you missed.
How much time
must I hear about this?
See you tomorrow, okay?
Yes, okay.
I'm sorry.
哈囉?
Yeah, I'm working on it.
I need a minute, Ronnie,
all right? Back off.
You know,
they're waiting for us.
You're trying to make
a fool of me?
Maybe you are a fool.
Maybe you all are.
Excuse me?
Why didn't anyone tell me
that the system,
like any Windows system,
might try an automatic update?
You know,
I follow your protocols
like a fucking robot
assuming you know everything.
But you don't.
I reviewed all the data
from SIGINT.
Everyone is sure the guard OD'd.
Police, Razavi Electronics,
everyone.
That's not what I mean.
This is war.
No, it's not like war.
It is war.
And in war, innocent people die.
Look.
If we...
If we were in that meeting,
you would understand
the significance
of what you've done
and how everyone appreciates it.
I am really impressed
by your ability to cope
with unexpected situations.
That's the reason we're able
to let you be out there alone.
How's your Hebrew?
What?
It's shit.
They take the piss out of me
when I speak it, so I don't.
Is that why
they assigned you to me?
The outsiders?
A British Jew
living in Germany.
Working for a country
that's not his.
How does someone with such
a tenuous connection to 以色列
to the cause,
get to be at the heart
of one of the most
sensitive operations?
Not tenuous. Not tenuous.
Unusual.
You're all doing
what they've been doing
all along.
Thinking of her a foreigner
that we can use
and not one of us.
Am I?
She didn't get
to a sensitive place.
It became a sensitive place
because she was there.
We were selling
the Iranian Government
nuclear technology.
Defective components.
Components
with tracking devices.
It became the
central arena because of her.
Because of us.
Because of my work with her.
Fuck.
Remember when we were
at the party in Niavaran?
When I was dancing,
you were talking to this lady
in a gold dress.
Do you know her?
I wanted to ask her something.
I don't know these people.
You don't know them?
You sure?
Maybe they are friends
of Nawser's.
I don't know.
What are you asking?
Hey, calm down.
We're gonna get there.
Yeah.
You look very nice.
Your hair is perfect.
What are you doing? Stop it.
Stop it...
Whatever you do,
don't speak to my sisters.
All right?
No, I'm serious.
Don't even listen to them.
Nice to meet you.
Hi.
- Nice to meet you.
哈囉.
This is 瑞秋.
瑞秋, this is Roya, Nasim.
- Shiva, my sister.
- Nice to meet you.
This is Maryam, Farid's wife.
Farid is my older brother.
He is, uh... over there.
Okay, uh, I have to go
for one minute, okay?
- Hi.
- So glad to finally meet you.
We thought he was hiding you.
- You are from 加拿大, right?
- Yes.
Don't mind them,
they always do that.
She asks if you teach
at Ali's school?
Yes. Oh, you're Ali's mom?
She says
that Ali told her
that you teach him sometimes
afternoon.
- Hm.
- So she wants to thank you.
He's a great kid.
You know who is that, right?
No, should I?
Farhad's ex-wife.
Well, I'm not surprised
she's here.
Because her family
is friends with the groom.
She and Farhad...
very bad divorce.
Mm-hm, hm...
He is asking
if she would marry him
for 1,000 gold coins
and a truck full of flowers.
The Meriye, it's like a gift
from the groom to the bride.
She can ask it
whenever she wants.
She answers
after the third time.
She says, "With the permission
of my parents
and my grandparents... Yes."
You didn't tell me
you were divorced.
I don't like to speak of it.
Did you know
she was gonna be here?
Is that why
you wanted me to come?
I don't mind.
I want her to know you're taken.
It's not just her, no.
It's her whole family.
They... They don't stop
calling me.
Are you having a good time?
Yeah.
Good.
Why did you argue
with your brother?
He's older.
You understand.
In Iran, that matters.
So he is, uh...
He's in charge
of the family company and...
He's always away.
I do all the work.
And somehow,
still, he managed to, uh...
- treat me like an employee.
- Hm...
I don't want to talk about this.
Come on.
You want something?
I get you chai,
- gaz... I serve you. It's okay.
- No. No, really.
I have to tell you something.
Um, I have to fly tomorrow
to visit my father.
You went to Europe
about three weeks ago.
I know.
I know, but, um...
They found some stones
in his kidney
and, uh, he's doing
some sort of treatment.
Why didn't you tell me?
I just learned.
I think he's gonna be okay.
But, you know...
I should go.
You don't speak of him
very much, you know.
You're from a good family.
You wouldn't understand.
He's very cold, my father.
Always has been.
You know,
even after my mother died,
it was just, uh...
him and me, and...
He was very strict.
Mm.
Ridiculed everything I did,
you know?
I felt like I had to lie
all the time and...
And I would start living
in my head.
I got so angry at one point,
even after my mother died
that I'd...
say, "How could you marry him?"
You know? How could you
marry him and just...
leave me with him.
You're flying to Turkey
next to the Iranian border.
My team will join.
You're going to drive a payload
into the country.
- Drive?
- Mm-hm.
Through the mountains.
What's the payload?
Five devices.
Flora Halles.
German archeologist.
Same age as you. Similar build.
She's worked in Iran
multiple times.
That will be your cover
until you drop the car
in 德黑蘭.
Driving bombs
into Iran?
It's your job to protect me
from things
I shouldn't be doing.
God,
it's a simple drive
on a route that we often use.
It shouldn't be a big deal.
It's a fucking huge deal!
Because I shouldn't be
doing this.
Hey. Hey.
What do you want?
You wanna leave Iran?
You sent a woman there,
and everything's about that.
But it's never discussed
or spoken about.
What do you mean?
I'm pregnant, 湯瑪士.
You have a protocol for that?
Why didn't you say anything?
I don't want it
on their feed.
I don't want all these
fucking people to discuss it.
I need your help, 湯瑪士.
Quietly.
- 瑞秋, I have to report this.
- You can't.
They're gonna yank you.
They're just looking
for an excuse.
Well, so why are you
even telling me?
Why?
You're unbelievable.
What do you think I'm doing?
I'm talking to you as a friend.
Thanks.
So she got you
to lie for her
and you proceeded with it?
Ops are always doing
that sort of stuff.
"Prove you're on my side"
kind of thing.
She wanted me
to transgress for her.
- Aren't you downplaying this?
- Downplaying it?
You know I was on a path...
I knew right then and there
it could destroy
my whole career.
And yet you did it.
Yes, I did it.
Okay.
She had some personal stuff
to take care of.
Have you told her
we're gonna run Farhad directly?
And do you really think that now
is a good time to tell her?
She'll need some time
to get used to the idea.
Can you guarantee
she'll help recruit him
once she realizes
she's on her way out?
- Sorry...
- No need to look at him.
Look at me. I'm gonna head
"Business as Usual"
starting next month.
Just don't tell anyone.
Hasn't been announced yet.
The decision
to pull her out
changed everything.
She would never have been given
the Turkey Border Mission
otherwise.
It was as if they wanted
to signal to her, to me,
that this chapter was over.
This is Gulal.
He and another driver
will wait for you at this point.
It's in your GPS.
Right here by this well.
He'd want to see
that you came alone.
The code is,
"Archeology is good in Iran."
Mm-hm.
They'll drive you
through the mountains
to the Iranian side.
Off-road through here.
There's no physical borders.
He's from a family
of Kurdish smugglers we trust.
We timed the operation
so you won't intercept
the Iranian Border Patrol.
But, if you do,
they'll deal with it.
They'll hide you.
Bribe them.
They do it all the time.
All right.
Two on this door,
three on the other.
Do I leave the keys in the car?
Yes.
The people pick it up.
We'll take it from there.
Good luck.
Hey!
What's your name?
Hey.
What's your name? Hey!
What's your name?
- No!
- "Good at Iran."
"Archeology good in Iran."
Iran.
What is it?
What's going on?
Hey!
- Army Iran.
- Huh?
Army Iran.
Go, go, go.
- Go where?
- Go.
Go here.
- Go here. Go here!
- I'm not going in there.
I'm not going in there!
Go here. Army Iran.
Go here, go! Go here!
Get out.
Get... No!
No!
Stop the car! Stop the car!
Stop the...
Damn.
Fuck.
Was I talking in my sleep?
Are you giving me
sleeping pills?
Farhad!
瑞秋?
How did this happen?
They don't know anything.
A bicycle ran into me
in Germany.
Ugh, I didn't think
it was gonna be this bad.
You had some internal bleeding.
You're lucky
you had a Razavi card on you.
They called me.
Hm, you're going to love this.
How does this work?
What is it?
Bombings.
Iranian scientists
of the nuclear...
- Scientists?
- Yeah.
Two different locations
in 德黑蘭.
Fuck.
What?
The scientists
were with their families.
Two children died.
What is it?
- You're shaking.
- This fucking hospital.
I can't take this anymore.
I hate the smell.
I can't...
I can't do this anymore.
Farhad...
This is not...
What's wrong?
I'm not...
This is...
I can't do this...
I can't do this anymore.
What, what, what?
What is it?
How is your father?
He's fine.
Yeah, much better.
When is the next time
you'll visit him?
Don't know. A few weeks.
Why?
We are constantly
getting offers now
to expand our business
from Belgium, Germany.
But, my brother,
he doesn't like the risk
because of the sanctions.
But these sanctions,
they're even on
chips you need
in a goddamn toaster oven.
The world
is so hypocrite about this.
It's okay for 以色列 and America
to blow up children,
but we can't have
the components for, uh...
medical equipment.
You can help me.
Me?
Next time you're in Europe,
pick up some things for us.
- Farhad...
- No, no, no.
Computer chips.
They, they look at you,
Australian passport,
they're not gonna bother you.
Please don't ask me to do this.
Nobody will stop you.
And, if they do,
we deal with it.
I'm not worried about me.
I don't think
you should get into this.
Don't you trust me
when I tell you
something is okay?
I tell you...
It is okay.
Okay.
The laptop you brought
houses 20 logic controllers
with our version
of the STEP 7 Software.
We started circulating them
in the black market
since February.
What's the story
he's telling you?
That it's for medical equipment.
Good.
So he's in the business now.
You need to find a way
to bring him here.
Here? To 萊比錫?
Why?
I mean, why would he?
The whole point is that
I carry that stuff
for him, right?
He's not cut out for this.
He's like a kid
trying to prove himself.
He's already used you
to smuggle
restricted technology.
Because we seduced him into it
with all these offers
from our companies.
Whatever, 湯瑪士.
Are you pulling me out?
No.
We're gonna approach him
as a German company
seeking to do business
with Razavi Electronics.
When he lands,
I want you to take him
to a French restaurant
called, "Chez Henriette."
Eat. Someone will join you.
Who? You?
You always wanted
to get your hands on him.
But you got your hands on him.
- See how that worked out.
- Fuck you.
Suits you.
You like it?
Made a reservation
at my favorite French restaurant
in town.
I ate on the train.
I'm not hungry now.
Okay...
Well, I'm hungry.
Are you gonna come with me?
What is it, Farhad?
Did you go to an abortion place
in 德黑蘭 last month?
I...
I did.
I'm sorry.
I should've told you, all right?
My period was late.
I freaked out.
I just went to some place and...
I wouldn't have done anything
without you.
I got scared.
And then my period came
the next day,
it was false alarm.
So you're going
to get rid of this
without me ever knowing.
No.
Of course not.
I can never tell
what is going on behind your...
I'm not pregnant.
I was never pregnant, all right?
We're all hiding stuff.
You too.
What do you mean "you too"?
- Now, who's wearing...
- What do you mean "you too"?
Farhad, I live in a country
where I don't speak
the language, all right?
And the only person I know
is you.
What do you think
that feels like?
- 哈囉?
- Your father died.
What?
- No, we're going to...
- You heard what I said.
But we're going for lunch.
Exit now.
We're on our way up.
What is it?
Farhad, I... I have to make
a phone call.
My father...
Just wait for me here,
all right?
I'll... I'll be right back.
Son of a bitch.
瑞秋.
Hey, what are you...
English?
You're involved in a plot
to carry items
that violate the sanctions
against Iran.
Your lady friend is going
to appear before a judge
and go to jail.
So will you.
We will also implicate
your company.
What happens from now on,
it's really all up to you.
Did you try to terminate
a pregnancy in 德黑蘭?
Did 湯瑪士 know about this?
I answered
this question already.
I did, yes.
But she refused to talk to me.
Why did you call her?
I wanted to see how she's doing.
Helping her conceal
her pregnancy ended your career.
- Weren't you angry?
- What? With her?
Because I was very involved
in her life.
You stopped giving a shit.
You threw her away.
You choose she's no use anymore.
Oh, so now it's our fault.
What did she do
in her year in 以色列?
Probably trying
to contact Farhad
or get information about him.
Farhad is not in 德黑蘭 anymore.
Look at this.
After burying her father,
she gave an interview to this...
I don't know, local town paper.
She got her picture
in the fucking paper.
This is two days ago.
She also filed for a taxpayer ID
in England.
She's upping
her British identity profile.
Why would she do that?
- Isn't it obvious?
- No!
To make it harder for you
to fuck with her on European soil.
Farhad is still part
of "Business as Usual."
He lives in Germany.
We're running false flag.
He thinks he works
for the Germans.
Did you know that?
No.
Is she trying to meet him?
Seems so.
But there's much more going on.
She spent a day
in Switzerland
after leaving 倫敦.
Which passport is she using?
Her real one.
How did she leave 以色列
without getting flagged
at the airport?
We're not there yet.
She's threatening
the entire operation.
We have no choice.
After all she has done for us?
She's an operative.
She's not just some asset
you can discard.
We're trying
to make contact with her.
Once we do,
we'll put you on the phone...
No, no, no. Please...
Let me be the first one
to make contact with her.
I'll talk her out of Germany.
But face-to-face.
I'll get her out.
No shots fired,
no mess to clean up.
So...
They think
if they send you, you...
can convince me
to recruit my brother?
Is that what they're...
No.
I'm not with them anymore.
You don't.
- No.
- How did you find me?
It took a really long time.
- I'm sorry.
- Stop, please.
I made my own mess.
I was too eager.
You know, in the beginning, I...
I was sure that...
I brought trouble to you.
You disappeared,
they told me you were in jail
because of the things
you brought back
that I told you to bring.
I tried to make a deal with them
to release you.
Only after many months,
I realized...
you were with them.
Everything that was between us
was for them?
Everything was a lie?
What do you want?
I came here to see you.
And I came here
to say I'm sorry.
I came here to try
and get you out of this.
Keep the phone
on the table.
The solution you're offering
is the only solution.
You came for her.
It's the truth. Use it.
I know, 喬. I will.
I'm sorry to hear
about your father.
Do you remember how angry
I got once when you called him?
Truth is
it really made me laugh.
Why?
He was such a...
British liberal.
You know, stuffy historian.
Hated 以色列. The idea of it.
I can just imagine
what his reaction was like.
He was pretty scary.
What do you want, 瑞秋?
My name is Ann.
What do you want, Ann?
湯瑪士, I called you yesterday
because I knew
they would pull you into this.
I'm really glad you're here.
I went to Switzerland.
I set up safe deposit boxes
with information
about "Business as Usual."
They're paid in advance
for one month only.
Here's proof
if they need it.
If they're not paid
by the end of the month...
The content will be made public.
I want out, 湯瑪士.
I don't wanna work
for them anymore.
I didn't wanna report to them
or do annual polygraphs.
I'm done.
And I want you to help me
negotiate Farhad's freedom.
Extricate him
step-by-step.
And I'll only follow up
with you.
Once that's done,
I'll give you the bank details
and the safe numbers.
Listen, you know
I have no interest
in exposing any
of this information.
Make them understand.
You're running around Germany,
assuming that they won't act
on European soil.
Well, you're wrong.
They're getting desperate.
You're an outsider,
you're a foreigner.
You're not really 以色列i
or really Jewish.
Got no formal tie.
To them,
you're just a British citizen
who's suddenly gonna drop dead
in 科隆.
I haven't so far.
Then they're waiting for me
to talk you out.
They won't dare.
They'll negotiate.
They'll hit you,
and no one will ever know.
You'll know.
Look, 湯瑪士. All my life,
I've done things thinking...
I just feel like
I've never really made
a decision that's just mine.
And this is it.
This is my decision.
Even if I'm gonna get shot
in the next five minutes,
I still did this.
Mm-hmm?
Don't let her leave the table. Make the offer.
If she walks,
we'll be forced to act.
Put the phone down.
- They know the deal.
- 湯瑪士,
don't let her walk.
They're here for me.
湯瑪士,
what the hell are you doing?
Get out of the way right now!
Run!